[{"answer": "Well, the sheriff's department just came out and spoke with reporters.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "What is the very latest on this manhunt for this very dangerous man?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "It's very difficult to tell.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Or do they fear the whole thing has been a trail he's laid down to put them off where he really is?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "The police have been vague.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "What else can you tell me about the kind of firearms he may have?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Something very significant.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Is it some anniversary of his time with the LAPD?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "It's a little difficult to tell because the people we've spoken to are people who knew him in much happier times, that he was much more bubbly, much more normal.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Is that what the police think they're dealing with, somebody who just has been harboring resentment and is now settling scores?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "It certainly is.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "It's a pretty worrying situation, isn't it?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well, the circumstances today were certainly extraordinarily tragic.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "What is your overview of what is going on here?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, certainly very chilling, and now that we know that he in fact is acting out on his concerns even more significant.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "When you hear the nature of that threat, what do you -- what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "First off, we don't know what the catalyst was.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Do you remember him?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "And you probably gave it to him when you met him when he was about to go off for military service, is that right?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Actually I only became aware of this other package about an hour and a half ago.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Any idea what that could be about or do you assume it has to do with the fact that you happen to be running the LAPD when he got -- he got laid off?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "That's correct, and it's very high mountains, very rugged mountains, and -- so if he's up in that area, incredibly difficult terrain to try and explore and search.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "It's about 18 miles east of Los Angeles?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Well, certainly I think as the police forces in the California area are encouraging citizens, one, if you see this individual, and he's a very distinctive looking individual, huge.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "What is the best thing that people can do if they have any sighting of this guy?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "No, the captain, if I understand it, had retired prior to my time at the LAPD, it was in the period of 2002-2009, so I had no awareness or any exposure to him.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Have you had any dealings with him?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "There's a tremendous amount of evidence of somebody who is extremely confused in this 6,000-word manifesto.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "And from all you've seen, from this manifesto that this gunman has put out, this alleged gunman, what is your reading of his state of mind and his motivation?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Clearly, this is not about attention.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "What is going on here?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Yes, I've known Monica and her family since Monica was about 11 or 12 years old.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Did you know her father?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Was that ever something she was concerned about?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Is everybody in a state of terror about this?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "I think we're 12 hours from the snow starting so we should know exactly at this point in time.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Are you any nearer to knowing?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Tomorrow morning.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "What day would that fly be?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Hard to say because there are so many aspects to it and so many different positions.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Where do you think we are with this whole gun control debate right now?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Absolutely no harm done if you do that, if you do it right.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "What is wrong with forcing through something which actually reduces the ability of the criminally minded and the mentally deranged from getting their hands on this gun that I'm currently being seen firing here?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, Dick is a friend of mine for 20 years.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "First of all, what was your reaction to him being fired by Fox and being called the worst pundit of last year?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "You mean Hurricane Sandy?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "No, it's somewhere in the middle.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Or is that really just a convenient excuse?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I'm a very, very big Marco Rubio fan.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "What was your reaction when you saw that?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Well, it has to be done very carefully, very uniquely.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "I mean, at what stage does the drone activity cease to be legitimate targeting of terrorism and become a kind of glorified, very brutal, very lethal fishing expedition?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "I'll tell you, I share that mother's joy.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "And they'll be curious, what kind of emotions do you go through when you hear of this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I would say surround yourself with family.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "What kind of advice would you give his mother if you had the chance?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Jaycee and I talk, yes.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Have you had the chance to talk to Jaycee about what happened with this little boy Ethan?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Active in the foundation, as we all are.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "How is her progress coming along?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Very well, thank you.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "And her two little children, how are they doing?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "That's what the privacy is all about, is the ability for them to live as normal a life as possible.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Are they able to lead a kind of normal life now?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "You know, I don't place a whole lot of thought on that.", "docId": "130207pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Does part of you wish he had, too, lost his life, when eventually the kidnapping was exposed?", "qSentId": 562}]